DIANE KORONGY

I'm a full stack developer with experience in Ruby on Rails, Javascript, React, and Swift+iOS. I have a passion for design and building meaningful products and contributing in teams. I get excited about puzzles, training others, creative growth, and new technology.

EDUCATION

Rutgers University, New Brunswick, NJ

BS in Information Technology with a minor in Statistics & Computer Science

May 2017

Flatiron School, New York, NY

Full Stack Web Development/Software Engineering Immersive Program

March 2019

RELEVANT SKILLS

- Programming Languages: Javascript (ES6), Ruby, HTML5, CSS3, SQL, Swift, R, SAS
- Libraries & Frameworks: React, Redux, jQuery, Angular, ExpressJS, Rails
- Tools & Platforms: Git, Heroku, Webpack, Babel, JSX
- Other: Technical Support, Project Management, Enterprise Client Relations/Support, Handling escalations, integrations

EXPERIENCE

iCIMS, Holmdel, NJ

Technical Support Engineer

June 2017 - July 2018

- Assist in the configuration, adoption, maintenance, and support of iCIMS ATS software at client's request
- Work to troubleshoot, recreate, QA test, detect and escalate software bugs
- Modified and created client documentation on specific features and upgrades to software
- Assisted in defining client business processes, best practices, co-manage implementation projects, train users, and facilitate overall success within various client organizations.
- Supported clients and users through troubleshooting, ticket creation and execution, asset management and training
- Partner with external vendors to configure and troubleshoot client integrations via Flat File and web services, API integrations
- Configure coding online client HR forms and applications using front end technologies, branding customer web pages
- Mentor and create new trainings and facilitate trainings to support new hire classes and internal teams
- Manage multiple concurrently running projects and client accounts while delivering a customer experience second to none
- Proficient in JIRA, Salesforce, ZenDesk, HRIS, CRM

Geek Squad, Manalapan, NJ

Consultation Agent

Jan 2016 - Feb 2017

- Educating clients hands on the proper use of old and new/advanced technologies through training appointments
- Led in individual NPS and service sales by ensuring the best services and technology solutions to customers
- Run troubleshooting tests and diagnostics to determine product needs and service solutions on client's malfunctioning tech
- Troubleshoot/ diagnostics on Mac, Linux/Unix, and PC devices, replacements such as hard drives, power supplies, memory cards, system networking, TCP/IP and DNS
- Replacement of nonfunctional hardware components and diagnostic for proper functionality, OS reinstallation and proper setup, software installation, virus removal, troubleshooting computers network connection and proper setup for optimal connectivity
- Data retrieval from non-functional Internal or External HDD's, flash drives
- Managed product shipping and receiving to service centers, creating service orders, filing paperwork
- Handled technical troubleshooting within an enterprise environment, including system crashes, slow-downs and data recoveries

Dow Jones, Princeton, NJ

QA Analyst, Knowledge & Training, and Customer Experience (Intern)

June 2016 - Aug 2016

- Analyzed business processes, worked side by side both teams, developing robust and efficient testing approaches to ensure a high quality product/solutions
- Record and report software bugs and usability problems to project managers for corrective action
- Worked on the design, develop, and evaluation of training programs
- Performed of a wide variety of planned clinical oriented functions and learning experiences
- Redesigned "wiki pages" for the Wall Street Journal and Barron's Training team for call service agents
- ACHIEVEMENTS, Dow Jones Business Plan Competition Winner Designed a high-fidelity user experience and interface of a mobile app prototype for The Wall Street Journal